voscreen.com 2015-06-07

# Voscreen - life itself

#### Privacy

This privacy policy sets out how Voscreen uses and protects any information that you provide to us when you use this website.

Voscreen is committed to respecting the privacy of visitors and the confidentiality of their personal data when browsing this website. Any information we ask you to provide, by which you can be identified when using this website, will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Voscreen may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. It is recommended that you check this page from time to time to ensure that you are not missing out on any changes. When this Privacy Policy is changed in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any of the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy please do not use Voscreen.

Voscreen intends and adheres to universal set of data protection principles included in applicable laws, by not sharing or making use of any private or personal data, with any of the users or any other third parties. Voscreen undertakes to make use of such information, only for big data and for general statistical, social, sociological, cultural, general psychological purposes, for scientific research and development for humanistic purposes and for improvement of lingual algorithms of Voscreen software and Voscreen.com at large.

##### Consent

By accessing this website, you are indicating your express and unconditional consent and agreement to the collection, transfer, processing, use and storage of any personal information, which may be obtained from you as a result of your use of the website. 

##### Collection of Personal Data, IP Addresses and Other Information

We may collect the following information:

  * Your name
  * Your contact information including your email address
  * Your demographic information such as your preferences and interests
  * Your language learning levels
  * Your IP address and visit details, including access time, browser type, referring URL and other technical information in relation to your visit
  * Other information that you may provide to our user surveys and feedbacks.

The website sends this data to Voscreen servers. We require this data to better attend to your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular:

  * internal record keeping
  * anonymous statistical analysis, such as tracking the number and location of visitors, as well as their activities while on this website (including the pages they view, the date and time of view, number of videos they watch, the questions they answer right or wrong and the videos they liked or disliked)
  * to provide the users with a better Voscreen experience by improving our products and services
  * to ensure the website’s safety, improve its operation and tailor the Voscreen content to users’ requests, in accordance with your interests
  * to update the users about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

##### Security

We are committed to ensuring the security of your personal information collected, as a result of your use of this website. In order to prevent unlawful or accidental destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized disclosure or access, or other unlawful forms of processing and to fully secure the information we collect online, we implement a variety of physical and electronic measures into our servers.

##### No Warranties

Voscreen does not provide any express or implied representations or warranties of any kind in relation to its ability to control, collect, correct, process, use, store, protect or transfer any personal information or does not guarantee the existence or effectiveness of any security measures. Voscreen will not be liable for access, disclosure, use or modification of your personal information by any third parties, or the damages due to computer viruses or other harmful elements and their effects on your personal information.

Voscreen, its affiliates, partners, and their respective employees, officers, directors or insurers will not be liable to you or to any other person for any costs, damages or liability of any nature, arising or resulting from the collection, use, transfer, processing or storage of personal information obtained by us due to your use of this website.

##### Cookies

The website may use cookies to remember the visitor in further visits, to help us provide you with a better online experience, by enabling us to monitor your preferences. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of Voscreen.

We use Google Analytics to provide us with information about how you use our website which we use to help us to improve our website. Google uses cookies as part of this process (please see [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) for more information).

##### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites from time to time. However, you should note that we do not have any control over the websites that you may connect through links from our website. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.

##### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * if you are asked to fill in a form on the website regarding personal data, please click check the decline box to let us know that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes,
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [privacy@voscreen.com](mailto:privacy@voscreen.com).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties, which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above e-mail address.
